-Hey. I got some bad news. -What?
-有個壞消息 -什麼？
That's no way to sell newspapers. Try, "Extra! Extra! Read all about it!"
那不是賣報紙的好方法 試試「快報，快來買喔」
No. Monica's restaurant got a horrible review in the Post.
不，摩妮卡的餐廳 在紐約郵報上的評價很差
I didn't want her to see it, so I ran around and bought all the copies.
我不希望她看到它 所以跑遍附近報攤買下所有報紙
Two, four, six, one million. Yeah, you got them all.
二，四，六，一百萬 對，你把它們都買回來了
This is bad. And I've had bad reviews.
這真的很糟糕 我一直都被批評的很凶
I remember my first good one:
我還記得我第一次被讚美
"Everything else in Our Town was terrible.
在《我們的小鎮》裡 其他的事都很糟糕
Joey Tribbiani was abysmal."
喬伊崔比亞尼是個無底洞
Oh, my God! Look at all the newspapers.
我的天啊 看看這些報紙
It must be a good review. Is it great?
評價一定很不錯，對吧？
Oh, dear God.
我的天啊
But the good news is, no one in a two-block radius will ever know.
但好消息是 兩條街裡沒有人會知道
-And the rest of Manhattan? -They all know.
-曼哈頓其他的人呢？ -他們都會知道
Oh, my God, this is horrible. I'm so humiliated.
天啊，這太可怕了 我覺得好丟臉
They say there's no such thing as bad press.
人家不是說沒有所謂的負面報導
You don't think that "the mahi-mahi was awful-awful" is bad press?
你不覺得「鬼頭刀難吃極了」 是負面報導嗎？
I didn't write it.
那又不是我寫的
-God, is he right? Am I awful? -Oh, no!
-天啊，他說的對嗎？我很遜嗎？ -不
Monica, listen to me.
摩妮卡，聽我說
I'm not just saying this because I'm your friend.
我這麼做 不只因為我是你的朋友
Your food is abysmal!
你的食物是個無底洞
The One With The Cooking Class
本集播出：烹飪課程
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
-Ross? -What? What?
-羅斯 -什麼？
-I am freaking out! -Are you?
-我快嚇死了 -是嗎？
My due date is in one week!
我的預產期是一星期後
-What are you doing up? -That is seven days.
-你為什麼不睡覺？ -只剩七天
I had a lot of water. Can we do this after..?
我睡前喝了太多水 我們可不可以晚一點再…
No, no, no, no, Ross!
不，羅斯
We don't have any big stuff we need.
我們沒有準備任何東西
We don't have a changing table or a crib.
我們沒買尿布台或搖籃
-We do not have a diaper service. -Funny you should mention diapers.
-我們甚至沒買尿布 -你現在提起尿布太有趣了
-I'm serious. -There's nothing to worry about.
-我是認真的 -沒什麼好擔心的
There's a baby store on West 10th. We'll go there..
西10街有家嬰兒用品專賣店 我們到那裡去…
-and get everything we need. Okay? -Okay. Thank you. That's great.
-買我們需要的東西，好嗎？ -好吧，謝謝你，太棒了
Where on West 10th? There's a shoe store..
西10街在哪裡？ 那裡有家鞋店…
Okay. If you're gonna do this, then I'm gonna go do that, so..
好吧，如果你要這麼做 我要那麼做，所以…
-Wait, Ross! I'm sorry, one more thing. -Yeah.
-等一下，羅斯，抱歉，還有一件事 -對
Our situation, you know, what we mean to each other..
我們的情況 我們對彼此的意義…
and, I mean, we're having this baby together and we live together..
我是說我們要一起撫養孩子 我們要住在一起…
Isn't that..? Isn't that weird?
那…那不是很奇怪嗎？
Well..
喔…
I'm just kidding. You can go pee.
我只是在開玩笑，你可以去上廁所了
Did we say we were gonna meet here or at the movie?
我們約好在這裡 或是在電影院裡碰面？
-We said at the movies, but.. -I'll see you there.
-我們約好在電影院裡碰面，但是… -我們到電影院見
-Now that you're here..? -I'll hang out till I have to meet you.
-既然你來了… -跟你們碰面之前先和你們混
-How come you're not going? -I've got a job interview.
-你為什麼不去？ -我要去面試一個新工作
-I thought you already have a job. -And they say you don't pay attention.
-我以為你已經有工作了 -大家還說你不太關心別人
It's a better job. It's vice president of the company..
這份工作比較好 它是一家公司的副總裁…
that does data reconfiguration for other companies.
這家公司為其他公司 做資料重構
-Wow. How do you know how to do that? -That's what I do now.
-你怎麼知道該怎麼做？ -那就是我現在的工作
-Joey? Come taste this. -What?
-喬伊，來試吃一下 -什麼？
Remember the guy that gave me a bad review? Well..
還記得給我爛評價的那個人嗎？ 喔…
I'm getting my revenge.
我要跟他報復
You cooked him?
你把他煮了？
No. He teaches a course at The New School..
不，他在新校 開了一堂課…
I want to make him try my bouillabaisse again.
我要他再試試 我的馬賽魚湯
I can't wait to read the front page tomorrow:
我等不及要看 明天的報紙頭條
"Restaurant reviewer admits: 'I was wrong about Monica.'"
「餐廳評鑒家承認： 我錯怪了摩妮卡」
The front page?
頭版？
You really do live in your own little world, don't you?
你真的活在你的小世界裡 對吧？
-I better get to my movie. -Oh, yeah.
-我最好快去看電影 -對
If I'm going to the movie and you're going to the movie..
如果我要去電影院 你也要去電影院…
why don't we just go together?
我們為什麼不一起去？
How's that for data reconfiguration, huh, Chand?
這個資料重構還不錯吧？ 錢德
My name's Katie if there's anything else you need.
我是凱蒂 很高興能為你們服務
Oh, God, I don't know. I want.. Everything is so great, I just want everything.
天啊，我不知道，我要… 這裡的東西好棒，我要通通買下來
Oh, look at this. We need this!
你看，我們需要這個
-What is it? -I don't know.
-它是什麼？ -我不知道
Have you ever had two people who weren't wearing crowns..
你們曾經有過 兩個客人不穿小丑裝…
spend this much money here?
卻在這裡花了這麼多錢的記錄嗎？
You have selected a lot of nice things.
你們選了很多好東西
You want these delivered, Mr. and Mrs. Geller?
需要我們做外送服務嗎？ 蓋勒先生跟蓋勒太太
-Oh, no, no. -No, no.
-不 -不
-We're not married. -We are having a baby..
-我們沒有結婚 -我們的孩子快出世了…
but we're not involved.
但我們沒有結婚
I mean, we were seeing each other a while ago..
我是說 我們曾經交往過…
but then we were just friends, and then there was one drunken night..
之後我們變成了朋友 有天晚上我們喝醉了…
Or, yes, stranger, we'd like this delivered, please.
對，陌生人 我們需要外送服務
-Can you fill out this address card? -Oh, okay.
-麻煩你填一下住址 -好的
-You picked out a lot of dinosaurs. -Yeah.
-你挑了很多恐龍 -對
That's one of the reasons why we're not a couple.
所以那也就是為什麼 我們沒有結婚
I chose those. I'm a paleontologist.
我選了那些，我是古生物學家
Really? That is so cool.
真的嗎？那太酷了
Don't get too worked up. It sounds like he's a doctor, but he's not.
別太誇他 你可能以為他是博士，但事實上不然
No. I'm fascinated by paleontology.
不，我喜歡古生物學
-Have you read the Walter Alvarez book? -I teach it in class.
-你看過華特艾瓦瑞茲的書嗎？ -它是我的教科書
Standing at a cash register, I'm holding a credit card, and I'm bored.
我站在收銀台，手裡拿著信用卡 卻覺得很無聊
I love your neighborhood. There's a great gym around the corner.
我喜歡你住的社區 街角有家很棒的健身房
-That's my gym. -I could tell you work out.
-那是我的健身房 -我看得出來你有健身
A paleontologist who works out. You're like Indiana Jones.
一位會健身的古生物學家 你跟印第安納瓊斯一樣
I am like Indiana Jones.
我是跟印第安納瓊斯一樣
-Hi, Pheebs. -Hey! Oh, how did baby shopping go?
-嗨，菲比 -寶寶的東西買得怎麼樣了？
Great! We got everything we needed.
太棒了，我們需要的東西都買到了
Oh, and Ross almost got something that wasn't on the list.
羅斯差點拿到 清單上沒有的東西
A whore.
一個妓女
What?
什麼？
We were paying, and this sales woman just started flirting with him.
我們正在付帳 這個女銷售員開始泡他
Can you believe that?
你能相信嗎？
-Did she know you two weren't married? -Yeah.
-她知道你們沒有結婚嗎？ -知道
Oh, my God. Well, the idea.. A woman flirting with a single man?
天啊，那… 一個女人在泡一個單身男人？
-We must alert the church elders. -No.
-我們得通知教會的長老 -不
You don't understand. You didn't see how brazen she was.
你不瞭解 你沒看到她多不要臉
-Sounds like you're jealous. -No, I'm not.
-你好像在吃醋 -我才沒有
I just think it's wrong. I mean, here I am, about to pop..
我只是覺得那是不對的 我是說我就快生了…
and he's out picking up some shopgirl at Sluts-R-Us?
他在蕩婦專門店泡女人？
Is that a real place?
真的有那種地方嗎？
Are they hiring?
他們有缺人嗎？
Hey, Phoebe. Fatty.
嘿，菲比，肥婆
Why so fancy?
你為什麼那麼高興？
I got a job interview.
我得到一個面試機會
It's more money, and I'd be doing data reconfiguration.
薪水比較高 我要做資料重構的工作
-I think I know someone who does that. -Me. I do that.
-我知道有個人就做那一行 -那就是我
So do I look okay? I'm nervous.
我看起來還好吧？ 我好緊張
Oh, yeah. You look great.
對，你看起來很棒
You know, just don't get your hopes up.
別抱太高的希望
-Why not? -Well, the interview.
-為什麼？ -你要去面試
-Yeah? -You know.
-所以呢？ -你知道的
You don't make a very good first impression.
你無法給人留下良好的第一印象
-What? -Oh, you don't know.
-什麼？ -喔，你不知道啊
-Are you serious? -When I first met you, you were like:
-你是說真的嗎？ -我第一次見到你，你是這樣的
I was like:
我就覺得…
What is it that I do?
我怎麼了？
It's just, like, you're trying too hard, making jokes..
你太努力想要說笑話…
You come off a little needy.
你太急了
Did you like me when we first met?
我們第一次見面時，你喜歡我嗎？
Chandler, I'm not gonna lie to you. But I am gonna run away from you.
錢德，我不想騙你 但我要離開了
She's put on so much weight.
她胖了太多
There he is.
他在那裡
That smug bastard.
天殺的王八蛋
Okay, class. We'll see you next time.
好了，同學們 下次見
There he is.
他在那裡
Hi. I'm Monica Geller, chef at Allessandro's.
嗨，我是摩妮卡蓋勒 亞利山多洛斯的主廚
Still?
現在還是？
The things you said were unfair..
你說的評論有點不公平…
and I want you to try my bouillabaisse again.
我要你再試試 我的馬賽魚湯
I don't see why I'd do that to myself again.
我看不出來 我有什麼原因再試一次
Either eat it or be in it.
你不吃就倒霉
Spoon?
湯匙？
-What do you think? -I'm torn..
-你覺得呢？ -我很為難…
between my integrity and my desire to avoid a beating.
不知道要老實說 還是避免自己被打一頓
But I must be honest. Your soup is abysmal.
但我得老實說 你的湯是個無底洞
Thattagirl! We should get out of here, there's a new class coming in.
做的好，我們應該離開這裡 新的一班要上課了
Welcome to lntroduction to Cooking.
歡迎大家來上烹調入門
Can anyone tell me the difference between hollandaise and bearnaise sauce?
誰能告訴我荷蘭酸味蘸醬 貝納斯醬的差別？
-I can. -Okay, go ahead.
-我知道 -請說
Well, they both have a egg yolk and butter base.
它們都放了蛋黃 跟奶油
But a bearnaise has shallots, chervil, and most importantly, tarragon.
但貝納斯醬有放蔥、雪維菜 跟最重要的小龍艾
-Very good. What's your name? -Monica.
-非常好，你叫什麼名字？  -摩妮卡
-You go to the head of the class! -Okay!
-你來當班長 -好吧
This stuff takes up a lot of room.
這些玩意占好多空間喔
How serious are you about keeping Ben in your life?
你說你要留班一輩子 你有多認真？
My son? Pretty serious.
我的兒子嗎？我非常認真
Hi, Katie. What are you doing here?
嗨，凱蒂 你來這裡做什麼？
The delivery went out and they forgot this.
外送部忘了這個
It must have been obvious, since it was the only thing left in your store.
這一定很明顯 因為它是你店裡唯一剩下的東西
Listen, to be honest, home deliveries aren't really part of my job description.
聽著，老實說 我的工作不包括送貨到家服務
Oh, I actually came here to ask you out.
我是來這裡約你的
Oh. Wow. Yeah, that sounds great.
哇 那聽起來很棒
I'm just gonna put this back in my pocket and pretend that didn't happen.
我要把這個放回我的口袋 假裝那件事沒有發生過
I'm free now. You want to get coffee..?
現在我有空 你要去喝咖啡嗎…？
-Sure. -Horny bitch.
-當然好 -蕩婦
No, you're a horny bitch! No, you're a horny bitch!
不，你是蕩婦 不，你是蕩婦
No, you're a horny bitch!
不，你是蕩婦
You guys have a good time.
祝你們玩得愉快
I'm just gonna grab my coat. And my whip.
我去拿我的外套跟鞭子
You know, because of lndiana Jones.
因為我像印第安納瓊斯
Not because I'm into S & M.
不是因為我喜歡性虐待
I'm not into anything weird, you know?
我沒有怪癖，你知道嗎？
Just normal sex.
我只喜歡一般的性愛
So I'm gonna grab my coat.
我去拿外套
So you had a good day, huh? Big commission, picked up a daddy.
你今天過得很不錯嘛？ 泡老爸賺大佣金
Are you okay with this?
你沒問題吧？
Oh, yeah. Yeah, please. You guys have fun.
當然，拜託 你們好好玩吧
-Okay. -Yeah.
-好吧 -對
Nice to see you.
很高興能見到你
Oh, and it was great to see you too. And you look fantastic.
我也是 你看起來好極了
-Although you missed a button. -Oh, actually, I..
-雖然你有顆釦子忘了扣 -事實上我…
Oh, okay, I see what you're doing there.
好吧 我知道你想做什麼
I can't even believe this. I really come off that badly?
我不敢相信 我的形象有那麼糟？
It's okay. You calm down after a while..
那沒什麼 不久後你會靜下來…
and then people see how wonderful you are.
大家會瞭解你有多棒
Good. Because I'm sure this interview will last weeks.
好吧，因為我相信 這次面試會維持好幾個星期
All right, don't freak out, okay? I will help you.
好吧，別驚慌 我會幫你的
-How long before you have to leave? -An hour.
-你什麼時候要出發？ -一小時後
-I can't help you. -Phoebe..
-我幫不了你 -菲比…
We'll do our best. I'm the interviewer and I'm meeting you for the first time.
我們得盡力而為，我是面試官 我第一次跟你見面
-Okay. -Hi. Come on in. I'm Regina Phalanges.
-好吧 -請進，我是蕾吉娜菲蘭吉斯
-Chandler Bing. -Oh, Bing.
-錢德賓 -賓
-What an unusual name. -You should meet my Uncle Bada.
-你的名字很罕見 -你應該見見我的巴達叔叔
I'll let myself out.
我自己出去
Your alfredo's dry. Did you use your cheese?
你的意大利寬條面有點干 你有放起司嗎？
When you say "use, " do you mean "eat as a pre-cooking snack"?
你說「放」是指 「把它當作菜前的點心吃掉了」嗎？
-And the cream? -Cheese makes me thirsty.
-奶油呢？ -起司讓我口渴
-Okay. Let's move on. -All right.
-好吧，我們繼續 -好吧
Something smells good over at Monica's station.
摩妮卡做的菜 味道很香
My God! This is amazing! You've never made this before?
天啊，這真的是太好吃了 你從來沒有做過這個？
Oh, no. I don't know anything about cooking.
不 我不懂烹飪
I had to ask what it was called when the water makes those bubbles.
我不知道水冒泡後 要做什麼
-Hats off to the chef. -Your mouth was full. I didn't hear.
-向主廚致意 -你嘴裡都是東西，我聽不到
-Hats off to who? -The chef!
-跟誰致意？ -主廚
That's right!
沒錯
You'll find that I don't micromanage. I don't shy away from delegating.
你會發現我不會事必躬親 我不害怕溝通
That's good to know. But let's stop focusing on what you don't do..
那真的很棒 但別談那些你不會做的事…
and focus on what you do do.
我們來談談你會做的事
What I do do..
我會…
is create an atmosphere of support for the people working with me.
支援為我工作的人
Nice sidestep on the "do do" thing.
你剛剛迴避的很巧妙
-Hardest thing I've ever done. -Oh, you gotta go!
-那是我做過最難的事 -你得出發了
-Don't worry. You're ready. -Really?
-別擔心，你準備好了 -真的嗎？
Absolutely! Just fight all your natural instincts, and you'll be great.
當然，跟著你的直覺走 你會很棒的
Monica, check these out.
摩妮卡，你看
Those look like cookies.
那看起來像餅乾
I know, yeah. And I made them all by myself.
我知道 完全是我自己做的
I mixed the ingredients, I put them in the oven, I took them out.
我混合所有材料 將它們放進烤箱裡再拿出來
Granted, I should have used the oven mitts, but still.
我不知道要用隔熱手套 但沒關係
Monica, my star student.
摩妮卡，我的明星學生
You called me that before, so I fashioned a star out of foil.
之前你那麼叫我 所以我用錫箔紙做了一顆星星
Now, no pressure. If you like my cookies, you give me the star.
別覺得壓力太大 如果你喜歡我的餅乾，給我一顆星星
Wow, a star!
一顆星星
I know you all hate me, and I'm sorry, but I don't care.
我知道你們都恨我 對不起，但我不在乎
-Okay, Joey, you're up next. -Yeah.
-好吧，喬伊，下一個是你 -是的
Oh, my God! This is amazing!
天啊，這真的是太棒了
You get an A.
你得到優等
I got an A? In school? Hey, I'm a dork!
我在學校裡得到優等？ 我是個書獃子了
Joey, I'm so proud of you.
喬伊，我非常以你為榮
-I think you should give him your star. -Excuse me?
-我想你該把你的星星給他 -你說什麼？
-He doesn't know what he's doing. -Nobody knows what they're doing.
-他不知道自己在做什麼 -初學者沒有人知道自己在做什麼
I do. I'm a professional chef!
我知道，我是職業主廚
Oh, relax. It's not a courtroom drama.
少來了，這又不是法律影集
Why are you taking Introduction to Cooking?
如果你是專業主廚 為什麼要上初級烹調課？
Yeah!
就是嘛
I'm sorry. I cook at this restaurant, Allessandro's..
抱歉 我是亞利山多洛斯餐廳的主廚…
and I just got a bad review.
我得到了很差的評論
-Allessandro's? I love that place! -You do?
-亞利山多洛斯？我喜歡那個地方 -是嗎？
You're a great chef. As a person you're a little..
你是個很棒的主廚 但你的個性有點…
-Oh, I'm crazy, but you liked the food? -Very much.
-我是很瘋狂，但你喜歡那裡的食物？ -非常喜歡
Okay, then. I don't stink. I'm a good chef! Okay.
好吧，那麼我不賴 我是個好主廚，好吧
I don't want to go. I'm having fun.
我不想離開，我玩得很開心
Did either of you pay for this class?
你們有付學費嗎？
Hey, if my friend says it's time to go, it's time to go!
如果我的朋友說 我們該走了，我們就該離開
I was the point person on my company's transition from the KL5 to GR6 systems.
我在我的公司負責KL5系統 轉換到GR6系統的工作
-You must have had your hands full. -That I did. That I did.
-你一定忙得不可開交 -沒錯，沒錯
So let's talk a little bit about your duties.
我們來談談你的責任吧
My duties?
我的責任？
All right.
好吧
You'll be heading a whole division, so you'll have a lot of duties.
你將負責一整個部門 所以你得負起很多責任
-I see. -But there'll be 30 people under you..
-我瞭解 -你手下會有30個人…
so you can dump a certain amount on them.
你可以把很多工作分給他們
-Good to know. -We could go into detail..
-那太好了 -我們可以仔細地…
No, don't, I beg of you.
不，我求你
All right. We'll have a definite answer for you on Monday.
好吧 我們會在星期一回覆你
But I can say with some confidence, you'll fit in well here.
但我相信 你在這裡會適應的很好
-Really? -Absolutely.
-真的嗎？ -當然
-You can relax. You did great. -Yeah, thanks.
-你可以放輕鬆，你表現的很好 -謝謝
I was really nervous. I'm told I come on too strongly.
我真的很緊張 大家都說我太喜歡講笑話緩和氣氛
And then it was really hard to sidestep that "duty" thing.
要避開「責任」的問題真的很難
Duties?
責任？
Doodies?
笨蛋？
Poo?
傻瓜？
Oh, my God. This doesn't count. Okay? The interview was over.
天啊，這不算，好嗎？ 面試已經結束
That was the real Chandler Bing. This is some crazy guy.
那才是真正的錢德賓 這只是個瘋子
Call security! There's a crazy guy out in the hall!
叫警衛來！ 走廊上有個瘋子
Poo?
傻瓜？
I'll look forward to your call.
我期待你的來電
-Hey. -Hey.
-嘿 -嘿
-You're back. -How are you?
-你約會回來了？ -你還好嗎？
I'm fine. But that's not important. What's important is how was she?
我很好，但那不重要 重要的是她還好嗎？
It was fun. We just had coffee.
我們玩得很高興 我們一起去喝咖啡
Oh, uh-huh, uh-huh, coffee, a little rub-rub-rub under the table?
喝咖啡在桌下調情？
What's going on? Do you not like Katie?
怎麼了？ 你不喜歡凱蒂？
No. No, she was nice. I mean, she was a little slutty, but who isn't?
不，她很好 她有點淫蕩，但誰不是呢？
Well, I liked her.
我喜歡她
Of course you did. You'd date a gorilla if it called you lndiana Jones.
你當然喜歡她，只要猩猩叫你 印第安納瓊斯，你也會跟他約會
Did you get a fresh batch of pregnancy hormones today?
你拿到今天的 懷孕荷爾蒙報告嗎？
No. It's just that.. Katie bothered me.
不，那只是… 凱蒂讓我覺得困擾
Why? What was wrong with her?
為什麼？她有哪裡不好？
There was nothing wrong with her. She was lovely.
她沒有哪裡不好 她非常可愛
-Okay. So, what's the matter? -I don't want you to date her.
-好吧，怎麼了？ -我不希望你跟她約會
Why? What, are you jealous?
為什麼？你在吃醋嗎？
Yes. And not because I want you to go out with me.
對 但不是因為我要你跟我交往
Because I don't want you to go out with anybody.
因為我不希望 你跟任何人交往
It's terrible to even think this and it's inappropriate..
光想到這一點我就不舒服 那是不對的…
but I want you to be at my constant beck and call,24 hours a day.
但我希望你每天24小時 都能陪在我身邊
I'm very sorry, but that is just the way that I feel.
我非常抱歉 但那就是我的感覺
-Okay. -What?
-好吧 -什麼？
I won't date. I'll..
我不約會，我會…
I'll be here with you all the time.
我會一直陪著你
Really?
真的嗎？
But I'm being so unreasonable.
但我的要求很無理
True, but you're allowed to be unreasonable. You're having our baby.
沒錯，但你可以無理取鬧 你懷了我們的寶寶
Oh, Ross, thank you. Thank you.
羅斯，謝謝你
You feel better?
你覺得好多了嗎？
No, not really. You're pressing the baby into my bladder..
真的沒有 你把寶寶壓在我的膀胱上…
and now I have to pee.
現在我得去尿尿
-Okay. -Rach?
-好吧 -瑞秋
-Yeah? -Just one thing..
-什麼事？ -只有一件事…
We live together. You're having our baby. I'm not gonna see anybody else.
我們住在一起，你懷了我們的孩子 我不跟任何人約會
Are you sure you don't want something more?
你確定 你不想更進一步嗎？
Wow. I don't know, maybe..
我不知道，或許吧…
Oh, Rach, I was just messing around.
瑞秋，我只是在開你玩笑
-Like you did when I had to pee? -Oh! I knew that.
-就像我要尿尿時你做的一樣 -我就知道
I knew that! I was just messing with you too!
我就知道 我也是在開你玩笑
Okay. Because for a minute you seemed..
好吧 因為你看起來似乎…
-No, it's just.. -Like you actually..
-不，那是… -像是你真的…
That's just because I'm such a good messer!
那只是因為 我很會開玩笑
-Rach? -Yeah?
-瑞秋 -什麼？
-The bathroom? -Right.
-你要上廁所 -對
I had a great time. I learned how to bake, ate great food.
我非常愉快，我學會了烤東西 吃美食
It's my first A since 7th grade and I didn't even sleep with the teacher.
這是我從七年級後第一次得到優等 我甚至沒有跟老師上床
-Oh, look. Acting for Beginners. -Yeah.
-你看，初級戲劇班 -對
-Wanna feel good about yourself? -What the hell!
-你想更滿意自己嗎？ -管它的
Let's start with some basics.
我們從基礎開始吧
Can anybody tell me what the difference between upstage and downstage is?
誰能告訴我 後台跟前台的差別？
Yeah, this was a stupid idea.
對，這個點子很蠢